<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lia Brüggemann</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lia Brüggemann</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Made with [Hugo](https://gohugo.io/) &amp; [Magnolia](https://github.com/ololiuhqui/magnolia-free-hugo-theme) by [Myself](https://github.com/BlyDoesCoding)

 Original Theme licensed under [MIT license](https://github.com/ololiuhqui/magnolia-free-hugo-theme/blob/main/LICENSE.md) 📄</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:16:02 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Donating to Free and Opensource Software Projects Is Important</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-donating-to-free-and-opensource-software-projects-is-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:16:02 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-donating-to-free-and-opensource-software-projects-is-important/</guid>
      <description>Digital networks were built for the purpose of sharing computing resources by people who were themselves sharing resources, technologies, and credit in order to create it. This is why digital technology is biased in favor of openness and sharing. Because we are not used to operating in a realm with these biases, however, we often exploit the openness of others or end up exploited ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steamdeck Modding Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/steamdeck/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:49:18 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/steamdeck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Steam Deck is a device that I became fascinated with instantly since it was announced. After using my LCD model for some time, I dived into the rabbit hole of modding it. I decided to write a comprehensive post about all the possibilities. Sit back, sip on your tea, and enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;accessories&#34;&gt;Accessories&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Having useful utilities for your deck can greatly enhance your enjoyment of using it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;sd-cards&#34;&gt;SD Cards&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re on a budget like me, you might have purchased a low-end 64GB (or lower storage in general) unit and simply need more space. The easiest solution is to buy an SD card and insert it into the easily accessible slot. Personally, I&amp;rsquo;ve had great experiences searching on Amazon for my desired size. It&amp;rsquo;s important to find one with adequate speed and capacity. Some even have &amp;ldquo;Steam Deck&amp;rdquo; in their description, which is usually a good sign. Nonetheless, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to check the reviews.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flowers Again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flowers-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:49:18 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flowers-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The summary on this page was left empty, so it was grabbed from the first content the theme can find on the page, which is what you are reading right now!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;A wreathèd garland of deservèd praise,&#xA;Of praise deservèd, unto Thee I give,&#xA;I give to Thee, who knowest all my ways,&#xA;My crooked winding ways, wherein I live,—&#xA;Wherein I die, not live ; for life is straight,&#xA;Straight as a line, and ever tends to Thee,&#xA;To Thee, who art more far above deceit,&#xA;Than deceit seems above simplicity…&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By George Herbert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CasaOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/casa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 12:10:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/casa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploring-casaos-for-server-revamp&#34;&gt;Exploring CasaOS for Server Revamp&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was eager to revamp my home server and embarked on a quest for new software projects that could breathe fresh life into it. That&amp;rsquo;s when I stumbled upon &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/IceWhaleTech/CasaOS&#34;&gt;CasaOS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;not-just-an-os-but-a-user-friendly-web-panel&#34;&gt;Not Just an OS, But a User-Friendly Web Panel&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Contrary to its name, CasaOS isn&amp;rsquo;t an operating system; rather, it&amp;rsquo;s a user-friendly web panel designed specifically for Linux servers. What caught my eye was its own &amp;ldquo;App Store,&amp;rdquo; a hub where I could effortlessly download popular server apps like Nextcloud or Jellyfin. The user interface is refreshingly minimalistic, making it a breeze to navigate. The installation process was a simple matter of copy-pasting a concise command. From the get-go, everything felt seamless.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
